A Bloody Legacy.
Candyman: Day of the Dead is a horror, thriller film directed by Turi Meyer.
As the Day of the Dead celebration approaches the barrio of East Los Angeles, Caroline is
challenged to control the horrifying legend of her ancestor, the "Candyman".
Candyman / Daniel Robitaille, played by Tony Todd.
Caroline McKeever, played by Donna D'Errico.
Tamara, played by Alexia Robinson.
Tino, played by Mike Moroff.
Miguel Velasco, played by Mark Adair-Rios.
David de La Paz, played by Jsu Garcia.
Candyman is an American supernatural horror franchise originating from the 1985 short story "The Forbidden" from the collection Books of Blood by
Clive Barker, about the legend of the "Candyman", the ghost of an artist and son of a slave who was murdered in the late 19th century.
Its film adaptation, Candyman, directed by Bernard Rose in
1992, starred Tony Todd as the title character.
Although the film initially underperformed at the
American box office, it became a cult classic.
A novelization
and a comic adaptation of the film
were released in the same year.
Two sequels, Candyman: Farewell to the Flesh (1995) and
Candyman 3: Day of the Dead (1999), were released.
A direct sequel to the original Candyman, directed by Nia DaCosta
and produced by Jordan Peele, was released in 2021.
The film explores themes of life and death, relatives,
murder, los angeles, california, bound and gagged.
The tone is dark and intense.